我是来自Google开发者关系部的Katherine Kwan  我之前在
I'm Katherine Kwan, and I'm a developer advocate at Google. I started off by
Android应用团队做过工程师  我为
working as an engineer on the Android apps team. I worked there for
Play商店和记事本应用程序Google Keep等Google产品做事
three years on products like Google Play and Google Keep, the note taking app.
在本课程中我会与大家交流基于这个平台你可以做什么
I'm continually blown away by what you can build on this platform, and
做些真正可以改善人们生活质量的应用程序
I'm particularly inspired by those apps that can truly improve people's lives.
当朋友聚会时  他们总是会给我描述一些非常伟大的手机软件创意
When I meet people, they often tell me about their great app ideas. But
但是他们并没有太多技术实力把应用做出来
then they feel like they don't have the technical skills to actually build it.
这也是我为什么转做开发者关系工作
And that's why I shifted over to developer relations so
因为它可以真正帮助大家做出来一些伟大的应用程序  通过本次课程
I can help people like you really build something great. Throughout this course,
我将会帮助你实现你的第一个应用
I'll be helping you implement your very first app.
[BLANK_AUDIO]
我是来自Google开发者关系部门的Dan Gauthan
>> My name is Dan Gauthan. I've been a developer advocate at Google for
我在这里工作了4年且身兼数职  我的目标是让我们一起把Sunshine
four years and I've worn a lot of hats here. My goal is to keep us on track to
这个应用程序做出来  这是一个接近产品级别的应用喔
make Sunshine, something that had some resemblance to a production quality app.
我将介绍Android的设计模式与原则  其中很多内容可能
I'll introduce Android design patterns and principles. Many of which are often
会照顾不到Android新手开发者  你要学会到如何使用框架
missed by new Android developers. You'll learn to lean on the framework,
专注如何让你的应用独一无二而不是重复造轮子
focusing on what makes your app unique instead of reinventing the wheel.
[BLANK_AUDIO]
我是Rado Mya  我在Google开发者关系部门工作过五年
>> I'm Rado Mya, and I've been a developer advocate at Google for five years.
我在还没有Android设备之前就开始Android开发
I started working on Androids so long ago that back then there were no devices.
当时我们所有的工作都在模拟器环境  很差的SDK环境下进行
All we had to work with were an emulator, a beater SDK, and
我为这个平台近乎狂热的付出过  我将用我扎实的
an almost fanatical devotion to the platform. I'll be joining you from here,
Android基础知识与你同行  我的目标并不是
my underground Android developer bunker, and my goal isn't to get you
赶鸭子上架  而是让你了解到我们为何
up an running as quickly as possible. It's to teach you the context behind
选择这样做  还有教你理解如何为移动设备做出
the choices we'll make. And the best practices you need, to really understand
感人用户体验的最佳实践经验
how to create great experiences specifically tailored to mobile devices. By
课程结束之后你就会知道下个应用该如何创建
the time you finished this course you'll know more than just how to create yet
你还会知道如何做一个专注于的用户伟大应用
another app. You'll know how to build great apps that focus on the user.